Good evening
Добрый вечер
Good evening from the city of Khmelnitsky
Добрый вечер из города Хмельницкий
Ukraine Where are you from
Украина Вы откуда
dry Abkhazia
сухом Абхазия
Georgia
Грузия
Abkhazia is Georgia
Абхазии это Грузии
No this is Abkhazia this is the territory of Georgia
Нет это Абхазия это территория Грузии
Sukhum
Сухум
is the territory of independent Abkhazia I am
это территория независимой Абхазии я
independent of the temporarily occupied
независимая от временно оккупированная
territory of Georgia in
территория Грузии
with Russian support yes
с российской поддержкой да
in 93 near your Light of Ministers
в 93 году возле вашего Света министров
still Shamil Basayev  danced
еще Шамиль Басаев танцевал
Now I’ll look at the
Сейчас я посмотрю
council took place against the backdrop of a burning one,
совет имел место на фоне горящего
I understood why Yes, yes, against the backdrop of a burning
я понял за что Да да на фоне горящего
Council of Ministers Yes, there are Chechens dancing
Совета Министров Да там чеченцы танцуют
like you were
типа вас было было
Chechens, this Basayev was and the company
чеченцы этот Басаев был и еще компания
stopped, that is, the Chechens were Russia
купировали то есть и чеченцы были Россия
was so, that is, there are Russian troops
была так то есть российские войска есть
you’re there No buddy you’re wrong
у вас там Нет дружище ты не прав
Russian troops are there
российские войска есть там вас
[music] there they
[музыка]
called you
есть вот именно позвали
in Moldova Yes
в Молдове Да
Russian troops in Donetsk Luhansk
российские войска в Донецке Луганске
called Russian troops
позвали российских
like this and you work
вот так типа и работаешь
recognized
признала
where not show where
где нет покажи где
in the eighth year it was didn’t recognize
в восьмом году это было не признала
Russia that you’re kidding  Well, to find where,
России что прикалываешься Ну найти где
oh damn Well, I
ой блин
made YouTube, for example, the eighth year, so
Ну сделал Ютубе например восьмой год вот
I look, I introduced it,
я смотри я ввел
and although yes it writes Russia recognized the
а хотя да пишет Россия признала
independence of Abkhazia on August 26, 2008
независимость Абхазии 26 августа 2008
Yes, I’ll look like it now That
года Да вроде оно сейчас посмотрю То
is, it turns out that Russia recognized you as a
есть получается вас признала
terrorist state,
террористическое государство Россия
then Nicaragua and Venezuela
потом Никарагуа и Венесуэла
that it belongs to Russia
ту она у России
They  some small island yes the same thing
Они остров какой-то маленький да
[music]
[музыка]
you already have very good international
у вас очень хорошие международное
recognition
признание он есть уже
why they don’t let a person in
а почему не пускают человека
and why did he decide for us to want a
а С чего это он решил за нас чтобы хотим
sense for you like this was the
смысле за вас типа вот это была
territory of Georgia
территория Грузии
when the territory of Georgia became Abkhazia
когда стала территория Грузии Абхазии
let's do it, let's go 91 90 years here the
давайте так давайте 91 90 года вот
Soviet Council was the territory of Georgia
Советском совета была территория Грузии
it was an autonomous republic within
это была автономная республика в составе
Soviet Georgia wait
Советской Грузии подожди
Abkhazia as part of Soviet Georgia entered
Абхазия в составе Советской Грузии вошла
in 1931 by force
в 1931 году это насильственным способом
and in 93 we forfeit our freedom
а в 93 году мы отваливаем свою свободу
What did you have there in 30 it  all
Что там был у вас там в 30 это все
fairy tales are like with Crimea, who came in when he came
сказки как с Крымом кто когда вошел
out here 45 was the Yalta
вышел вот 45 год был Ялтинская
conference,
конференция
he was unchanged to the borders
он неизменности до границ
and the Soviet Union when
и Советский Союз когда
no no did not change The Soviet Union
нет нет не изменилось Советский Союз
broke up the daughter exactly along the
распался дочь в точь-в-точь по
borders of the administrative republics
границам республик административным
just like here, see the
также как вот смотри
Armenian-Azerbaijani conflict Yes  that there
армяно-азербайджанский конфликт Да что
was Karabakh on the territory of Azerbaijan and
на территории Азербайджана был Карабах и
the Armenians believed that their
армяне считали что своей территории
ethnic territory was once something, the whole
этнической когда-то что-то вот все
conflict is coming to an end Yes, the Armenians
конфликт приходит к концу Да армяне
already recognize Yes, what
признают уже Да что
will this territory of Azerbaijan be
будет эта территория Азербайджана потому
because the world community
что мировое сообщество
recognizes the borders of these states along the
признает границы этих государств по
borders of the republics, so it is
границам республик так есть
when
когда
Georgia  how Independently the country
Грузия как Независимо уже страна
has already returned
вернулась
like this on and returned it first
вот так на и вернулась она сперва
returned to 1925 the Constitution that
вернулась в 1925 год Конституция которая
was written
была написана
then by
тогда
the hands of Abkhazia did not enter this thereby
руки Абхазии не входила это тем самым
she said to
она сказала
fornicate there in short the Constitution is not the
блудить короче там Конституция не
Constitution the world community until it
Конституция мировое сообщество до
recognizes this territory of society if it
признает это территории общества если
does not recognize me it does not mean  that
меня не признает это не означает что он
he doesn’t exist, you understand
меня не существует понимаешь
that you are right Not protected by the world
то что вы права Не защищены мировым
community, for this I’m watching, I’ll
сообществом для этого наблюдаю я тебе
just explain to you that you, as I understand it,
просто объясню что ты вот я так понимаю
that you still support What many
что ты ещё поддерживаешь Какие многие
Abkhazians support the military operation in
абхазы поддерживают военную операцию в
Ukraine,
Украине да
and the fact that I support it does not mean that I
то что я поддерживаю это не означает что
don’t know  there I'm asking for a military operation
не знаю там Я спрашиваю военную операцию
in Ukraine
в Украине
now look I'll tell you what the
теперь смотри я тебе расскажу что такое
world communication is
мировое сообщение
I'll explain how it works yes look
я объясню как оно работает да смотри
you Russian troops
вас российские войска
have occupied the region
оккупировали регион
after the Russian Federation
после того как Российская Федерация
falls apart it's going to collapse
развалится она идет к своему распаду
because it's dying attacked Ukraine
потому что она погибает напал на Украину
its army is being destroyed
ее армия уничтожается
bloc  NATO and the
блок НАТО и
entire world community support
все мировое сообщество поддерживает
Ukraine with serious weapons When the
Украину серьезным вооружение Когда
Russian army dies,
Российская армия сдохнет на окончательно
all these
будут окончательно решены все вот эти
conflicts in the post-Soviet space will be finally resolved,
конфликты на постсоветском пространстве
including
в том числе
very simply, then look at Moldova
очень просто значит смотрите в Молдову
Yes, in Transnistria, or peacekeepers will come out
Да в Приднестровье или выйдут Миротворцы
or Ukraine will enter, after that peacekeepers will come
он или войдет Украина после этого идут
to you  he will ask
Миротворцы у вас
us to ask Moldova to
попросит нас попросит Молдова чтобы
help her resolve this issue with
помочь ей решить этот вопрос посыльному
our messenger agreement and that’s it, and
договору нашим и все а у вас
he will make a decision with you When Russia is already
он примет решение Когда Россия уже будет
resting, he will decide to bring in
отдыхать примет решение ввести
peacekeepers
миротворцев
and there will be a transfer of power to Georgia absolutely
и будет передача власти Грузии абсолютно
everything is fine everything how According to international
все нормально все Как По международному
law, of course you will What is
праву вы конечно будете Чего Это
normal
нормально
vice versa  so that there will be no war, there will be
наоборот чтобы не было войны будут
peacekeepers, that is, you didn’t say that the
Миротворцы он то есть вы не говорили что
Georgians are slaughtering you there or something, a fairy
вас там грузины вырезают там или что-то
tale that will
сказка которая
come in Peacekeepers, of course
зайдут Миротворцы у вас конечно будет у
you will
вас будет
have your own, for example, some opinion Yes,
будет своё например какое-то мнение Да
you will say there, I would not really want to
вы скажете там я бы не очень хотел чтобы
Peacekeepers, he came in. I would like to
Миротворцы он заходили Я бы хотел чтобы
return to the time when Russia was a
вернулся в то время когда Россия была
strong and great power, But you
сильной и великой державой Но ты же
already understand what Russia is if we
понимаешь уже Что такое Россия если мы
bomb the territory of the
блин Э бомбим короче территорию
Russian Federation in short, he bombed the build region.
Российской Федерации он билдскую область
Yes, the Kremlin was bombed.
Да Кремль бомбили Ну это всё это уже
and all of you will be released
и всё вас освободят
I understand that you can’t say what you think in
Я понимаю что тебе нельзя говорить там в
this
этом
Yes, because you
то что ты думаешь Да потому что тебя
will again have authorities One of the resorts
снова будет Курортное одно из курортной
will have
будет
permission from yours to
разрешение с вашего хорошо
look well here I am Abkhaz so
смотреть вот я Абхаз так
I don’t consider the territory of Abkhazia the
Я не считаю территории Абхазии
territory of Georgia Where to
территории Грузии
look From what  fright and by what
искать С какого перепугу и по какому
right does Georgia want anything I don’t know
праву Грузия хочет что-либо не знаю
[music]
[музыка]
treat us how to tell the territory
относиться к нам как сказать территории
from which the
с чего
truth is very good just very good
правду очень хорошо просто очень хорошо
look, for example, Ukraine in 91
смотри например вот Украина в 91 году
also became the independence of such
тоже стало независимость таких
territories of Ukraine
территориях Украины
For example, we have a district in the Transcarpathian region
Например у нас в Закарпатской области
Where they live mainly in
есть район Где живут преимущественно
Hungary, they can take something, we
Венгрии они могут взять что-то мы короче
live here in Ukraine, like, yes, Ukraine
живем тут в Украине типа да вот Украина
took place as a state in such
состоялась как государство в таких
all loadings did not take place in such Georgia
всё погрузы не состоялась в таких Грузия
took place Such a nut in such
состоялась Таких вот орех в таких
territories The Soviet Union The Soviet
территориях Советском Союзе Советском
Union it was in such territories Yes
Союзе она была в таких территориях Да
Absolutely  right, well, this is the Soviet
Абсолютно верно хорошо это Советский
Union, the time has already passed. You yourself said
Союз пройденный уже время Ты сам сказал
this
об этом
in fact. I told you that after the
по факту Я тебе сказал что после
Soviet era I will return to the Constitution of
советского времени вернусь Конституции
25 years
25 года
and what kind of Soviet Union
а какая Советский Союз
the Soviet Union
Советский Союз
does not need anything well absolutely
ничего не нужно хорошо абсолютно никуда
we will not return anywhere just in fact In the
не возвращаемся просто по факту В
ninety-second year on August 14,
девяносто втором году 14 августа
ninety  the second year,
девяносто второго года
Georgian
грузинская
troops entered the Donetsk region
войска вошли в донецкую область
Abkhazia was the territory of Georgia in 91
Абхазия была территория Грузии в 91 году
in fact no
по факту нет
legally Yes and in fact yes That is, how did the
юридически Да и по факту да То есть как
Georgian troops enter the territory of
это войска Грузии вошли на территорию
Georgia, it turns out how it
Грузии получается как это так
didn’t happen
не было
Tell me tell me about the genocide of
Расскажи мне расскажи мне про геноцид
Georgians Where did
грузинов Куда делись
the Georgian  population of Abkhazia Well, tell me,
грузинское население Абхазии Ну расскажи
I remember how many refugees there were, I
Я помню вот эти сколько беженцев было я
remember
помню
in Abkhazia in Abkhazia Georgians lived before 92
в Абхазии в Абхазии жили грузины до 92
where they
куда они
left Why What happened
уехали А почему Что случилось
to their country to leave they lived they were
к себе в страну уехать они жили они там
born there not grandfathers were born they from
родились не деды родились они испокон
time immemorial there lived a lot of sternums so on
веков там много жила грудин так на
no one lived on the territory, I’m telling you since the
территории никто не жил я тебе говорю с
30s since the 30s When Stalin
30-х годов с 30-х годов Когда Сталин
united us with Georgia in a tyrannical way, he
васильственным способом нас соединил с
began to be resettled, building the so-
Грузией начался переселен строит так
called program that was not
называется программа которая не
carried out until the nineties Well,
осуществляли до девяностых годов Ну вот
until the end of the Soviet Union, it turns out
до конца Советского Союза то получается
To be honest,
Если честно
what happened
что случилось
What  it happened that the Georgians disappeared in
Что случилось что грузины пропали в
Abkhazia Well, what happened
Абхазии Ну что случилось
happened
случилось
[music]
[музыка]
Tell me about the genocide of Georgians in
Расскажи мне про геноцид грузин в
Abkhazia I
Абхазии
tell
рассказываю смеешься
you laughing at me how and what you have to
Надо мной как и что тебе должен
tell this to the fact I tell the truth I’m telling
рассказать это факту говорит правду
some I’ll look at the berries I
говорю какие-то Я сейчас посмотрю ягод я
don’t remember the exact date there was
точно числа не помню там была
if  I’m not mistaken, there were about
если я не ошибаюсь было около
half a million Georgian refugees Yes,
полумиллиона беженцев грузинских Да из
about half a million from Abkhazia I’ll
Абхазии около полумиллиона Я сейчас
look now we had a total of half a million
посмотрю у нас всего было полмиллиона
people in the country And now
населения в стране А сейчас 200.000
there are 200,000 Wikipedias Yes, ethnic cleansing of
вот есть Википедии Да этнически чистки
Georgians in Abkhazia Open it up, we can
грузин в Абхазии Вот открой может
read it together Maybe they
почитаем вместе Может там что-то
write something false, we’ll analyze Wikipedia  what is
неправду пишут разберём Википедия то что
written I don’t care
написано Мне без разницы
about specific facts that they just came up with
есть на конкретные факты что придумали
just
просто
Wikipedia and edit it myself there is a
Википедию и сам редактировать там
link for rent Here is a link to an
сдаётся ссылка Вот и ссылка на
international
международную
document
документ
well okay say there were murders of Georgians
хорошо ладно скажи были убийство грузин
in Abkhazia
в Абхазии
of course the war was
конечно война была
not military civilian Georgians there were
не военных гражданских грузин были
murders in Abkhazia
убийство в Абха
Of course because  they lived here That
зии Конечно потому что они здесь жили То
is, you killed them because they lived there,
есть их вы их убивали потому что они там
we
мы
[music] did
[музыка]
not touch the targeted population
целенаправленное население не трогали
no deportation of Georgians there were
нет депортации грузин были
no deportations
депортации не было
after the war after September 30, 903,
после войны после 30 сентября 903 года
many Georgians are
многие грузины
opening in
вот открываем
1992, Georgians accounted for up to half of
1992 года грузины составляли до половины
the population of Abkhazia according to official  there
населения Абхазии по официальным данным
were about 20 percent of the data there, and up
было там около 20 процентов а грузин
to half of the Georgians
до половины
[music]
[музыка]
YouTube driving us through Georgiev’s car into a
YouTube загоняя нас через кар Георгиев в
shadow ban and a rich look is not
теневый бан и дужебогатого вида не
shown to people in private,
показывается людям в частном на
information about streams is shown
показывается информация про стримы тому
in order to be a little operational beast
для того чтобы мало оперативный зверезок
Sign right at a time and try there in
Подпишите прям за раз а попыт там в
kilogram about Krim video
килограмме о Крим видео
and selfish information and we are with you on a
и корыстная информация и мы с вами по
stylish operational stars
стильной оперативной звездок
Total type how do you YouTube Glory to Ukraine
Итого типа как вам YouTube Слава Украине
subscribe
подпишись